{"id": 96, "data": "printed by W. B. for Robert Knaplock", "label": [[11, 16, "PERSON"], [21, 36, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 97, "data": "printed for J. Peele at Locke's Head in Amen-Corner, Paternoster-Row", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [40, 51, "LOC"], [53, 68, "LOC"], [24, 36, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 98, "data": "Printed at Dublin: London, reprinted and sold by T. Warner", "label": [[11, 17, "LOC"], [19, 25, "LOC"], [49, 58, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 99, "data": "Printed at Dublin: London, reprinted and sold by T. Warner at the Black-Boy in Pater-Noster-Row", "label": [[11, 17, "LOC"], [19, 25, "LOC"], [49, 58, "PERSON"], [79, 95, "LOC"], [62, 75, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 100, "data": "Printed by W. Bowyer: and sold by James and John Knapton, A. Bettesworth, J. Osborn and T. Longman, J. Noon, and J. Clark at the Royal-Exchange", "label": [[11, 20, "PERSON"], [34, 56, "ORG"], [58, 72, "PERSON"], [74, 98, "ORG"], [100, 107, "PERSON"], [113, 121, "PERSON"], [125, 143, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 101, "data": "printed by W. Botham, for James and John Knapton", "label": [[11, 20, "PERSON"], [26, 48, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 102, "data": "printed for J. Peele at Locke's Head in Pater-Noster Row", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [40, 56, "LOC"], [24, 36, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 103, "data": "printed for T. Warner; and sold by the booksellers of London and Westminster, Oxford and Cambridge", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [54, 60, "LOC"], [65, 76, "LOC"], [78, 84, "LOC"], [89, 98, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 104, "data": "printed for John Pemberton, at the Buck, against St. Dunstan's Church, in Fleet-Street", "label": [[12, 26, "PERSON"], [49, 69, "LOC"], [74, 86, "LOC"], [31, 39, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 105, "data": "Printed at Dublin. London: reprinted and sold by A. Moor in St. Paul's Church-Yard, and the booksellers of London and Westminster", "label": [[11, 17, "LOC"], [19, 25, "LOC"], [49, 56, "PERSON"], [60, 82, "LOC"], [107, 113, "LOC"], [118, 129, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 106, "data": "printed for Richard Williamson", "label": [[12, 30, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 107, "data": "printed for W.Innys at the West End of St. Paul's", "label": [[12, 19, "PERSON"], [27, 49, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 108, "data": "Printed by W. Bowyer for the Company of Stationers", "label": [[11, 20, "PERSON"], [29, 50, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 109, "data": "Printed for Bernard Lintot, at the Cross-Keys, between the Temple-Gates in Fleet-street", "label": [[12, 26, "PERSON"], [59, 71, "LOC"], [75, 87, "LOC"], [31, 45, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 110, "data": "prostant venales apud C. Davis, in vico vulgo dicto Pater-Noster-Row", "label": [[22, 30, "PERSON"], [52, 68, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 111, "data": "printed for Fletcher Gyles, over-against Gray's-Inn, Holborne", "label": [[12, 26, "PERSON"], [41, 51, "LOC"], [53, 61, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 112, "data": "printed for James and John Knapton, in St. Paul's Church-Yard; and C. Davis in Pater-Noster-Row", "label": [[12, 34, "ORG"], [39, 61, "LOC"], [67, 75, "PERSON"], [79, 95, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 113, "data": "printed for Cha. Davis in Pater-Noster-Row", "label": [[12, 22, "PERSON"], [26, 42, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 114, "data": "printed for J. and J. Bonwicke, at the Red Lion, in St. Paul's Church-Yard", "label": [[12, 30, "ORG"], [52, 74, "LOC"], [35, 47, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 115, "data": "printed for John Brindly at the King's-Arms in New-Bond-Street", "label": [[12, 24, "PERSON"], [32, 43, "LOC"], [47, 62, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 116, "data": "printed for Benjamin Motte, at the Middle-Temple-Gate, Fleetstreet, and sold by Weaver Bickerton, at the Lord Bacon's Head without Temple Bar, and Lawton Gilliver, at Homer's Head over against St. Dunstan's Church, Fleetstreet", "label": [[12, 26, "PERSON"], [35, 53, "LOC"], [55, 66, "LOC"], [80, 96, "PERSON"], [105, 122, "LOC"], [131, 141, "LOC"], [167, 179, "LOC"], [193, 213, "LOC"], [215, 226, "LOC"], [147, 162, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 117, "data": "printed for J. Peele, at Locke[s]-Head in Pater-Noster-Row", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [25, 38, "LOC"], [42, 58, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 118, "data": "printed for Benjamin Motte, at the Middle-Temple-Gate, Fleetstreet, and sold by Weaver Bickerton, at the Lord Bacon's Head without Temple Bar, and Lawton Gilliver, at Homer's Head over against St. Dunstan's Church, Fleetstreet", "label": [[12, 26, "PERSON"], [35, 53, "LOC"], [55, 66, "LOC"], [80, 96, "PERSON"], [131, 141, "LOC"], [147, 162, "PERSON"], [167, 179, "LOC"], [193, 213, "LOC"], [215, 226, "LOC"], [101, 122, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 119, "data": "printed for J. Peele at Locke's Head in Pater-Noster Row", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [24, 36, "LOC"], [40, 56, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 120, "data": "printed by William Bowyer, Jun. sometimesStudent of the same College; and sold by W. Thurlbourn in Cambridge, R. Clements in Oxford, and the booksellers of London and Westminster", "label": [[11, 31, "PERSON"], [82, 95, "PERSON"], [99, 108, "LOC"], [110, 121, "PERSON"], [125, 131, "LOC"], [156, 162, "LOC"], [167, 178, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 121, "data": "printed for J. Peele at Locke's Head in Pater-Noster Row", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [24, 36, "LOC"], [40, 56, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 122, "data": "printed for John Brindley, at the King's-Arms in New Bond-Street; and sold by A. Dodd, near Temple-Bar; J. Roberts, in Warwick-Lane; E. Nutt, and J. Smith, at the Royal-Exchange", "label": [[12, 25, "PERSON"], [49, 64, "LOC"], [78, 85, "PERSON"], [92, 102, "LOC"], [104, 114, "PERSON"], [119, 131, "LOC"], [133, 140, "PERSON"], [146, 154, "PERSON"], [30, 45, "LOC"], [159, 177, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 123, "data": "Printed for Richard Williamson near Gray's-Inn-Gate in Holborn", "label": [[12, 30, "PERSON"], [36, 51, "LOC"], [55, 62, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 124, "data": "printed by William Bowyer", "label": [[11, 25, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 125, "data": "printed for T. Warner at the Black-Boy in Pater-Noster-Row", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [42, 58, "LOC"], [25, 38, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 126, "data": "printed for Richard Williamson near Gray's-Inn-Gate in Holborn", "label": [[12, 30, "PERSON"], [36, 51, "LOC"], [55, 62, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 127, "data": "printed for F. Cogan, at the Middle-Templ[e] Gate in Fleet-Street", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [29, 49, "LOC"], [53, 65, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 128, "data": "Printed by A. Wilde, for the Company of Stationers", "label": [[11, 19, "PERSON"], [29, 50, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 129, "data": "typis Gulielmi Bowyer", "label": [[6, 21, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 130, "data": "printed for Richard Williamson", "label": [[12, 30, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 131, "data": "printed for Robert Gosling, at the Mitre and Crown against Fetter-Lane in Fleetstreet", "label": [[12, 26, "PERSON"], [59, 70, "LOC"], [74, 85, "LOC"], [31, 50, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 132, "data": "printed for F. Cogan, at the Middle-Temple Gate, in Fleetstreet", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [29, 47, "LOC"], [52, 63, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 133, "data": "printed for Richard Williamson, and William Bowyer", "label": [[12, 30, "PERSON"], [36, 50, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 134, "data": "William Bowyer", "label": [[0, 14, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 135, "data": "printed for S. Austen at the Angel and Bible in St. Paul's Church-Yard; and W. Bowyer, in White-Fryars", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [48, 70, "LOC"], [76, 85, "PERSON"], [90, 102, "LOC"], [25, 44, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 136, "data": "printed for W. Innys at the West End of St. Paul's", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [28, 50, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 137, "data": "printed for J. and J. Knapton, R. Williamson, T. Wotton, D. Brown, and T. Osborne", "label": [[12, 29, "ORG"], [31, 44, "PERSON"], [46, 55, "PERSON"], [57, 65, "PERSON"], [71, 81, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 138, "data": "Printed for Richard Williamson near Grays-Inn-Gate in Holborn", "label": [[12, 30, "PERSON"], [36, 50, "LOC"], [54, 61, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 139, "data": "impensis R. Gosling ad Insigne Mitrae & Coronae in Vico vulgo vocato Fleet-Street", "label": [[9, 19, "PERSON"], [31, 47, "LOC"], [69, 81, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 140, "data": "printed by J. Bettenham, for Christian Bowyer at the Rose in Pater-Noster-Row", "label": [[11, 23, "PERSON"], [29, 45, "PERSON"], [61, 77, "LOC"], [49, 57, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 141, "data": "printed for Samuel Ballard, Benj. Mott, Richard Williamson, Samuel Birt, Thomas Osborne, Charles Davis and David Lyon", "label": [[12, 26, "PERSON"], [28, 38, "PERSON"], [40, 58, "PERSON"], [60, 71, "PERSON"], [73, 87, "PERSON"], [89, 102, "PERSON"], [107, 117, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 142, "data": "printed for G. Strahan, W. Mears, S. Ballard, F. Clay, J. Hooke, B. Motte, R. Williamson, and the executors of H. Rhodes", "label": [[12, 22, "PERSON"], [24, 32, "PERSON"], [34, 44, "PERSON"], [46, 53, "PERSON"], [55, 63, "PERSON"], [65, 73, "PERSON"], [75, 88, "PERSON"], [98, 120, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 143, "data": "printed for G. Strahan, W. Mears, S. Ballard, F. Clay, J. Hooke, B. Motte, R. Williamson, and the executors of H. Rhodes", "label": [[12, 22, "PERSON"], [24, 32, "PERSON"], [34, 44, "PERSON"], [46, 53, "PERSON"], [55, 63, "PERSON"], [65, 73, "PERSON"], [75, 88, "PERSON"], [98, 120, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 144, "data": "printed for A. Millar, at Buchanan's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 41, "LOC"], [56, 76, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 145, "data": "printed for R. Gosling", "label": [[12, 22, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 146, "data": "Printed for A. Millar, at Buchanan's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 41, "LOC"], [56, 76, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 147, "data": "Printed for A. Millar, at Buchanan's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 41, "LOC"], [56, 76, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 148, "data": "printed for A. Millar, at Buchanan's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 41, "LOC"], [56, 76, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 149, "data": "Printed for A. Millar, at Buchanan's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 41, "LOC"], [56, 76, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 150, "data": "printed for T. Osborne, in Gray's-Inn", "label": [[12, 22, "PERSON"], [27, 37, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 151, "data": "printed for J. and J. Knapton, D. Midwinter and A. Ward. W. Innys, J. Osborn and T. Longman, R. Robinson, and R. Williamson", "label": [[12, 29, "ORG"], [31, 55, "ORG"], [57, 65, "PERSON"], [67, 91, "ORG"], [93, 104, "PERSON"], [110, 123, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 152, "data": "printed for J. Walthoe Sen. R. Vincent Sen. J. and J. Knapton, R. Knaplock, J. Roberts, J. Darby, S. Buckley, D. Midwinter and A. Ward, A. Bettesworth and C. Hitch, B. Lintot, R. Gosling, W. Mears, B. Sprint, J. Tonson, W. Innys, J. Osborn and T. Longman, T. Woodward, R. Robinson, T. Saunders, B. Motte, J. Walthoe Jun. C. King, F. Clay, W. Battersby, J. Batley, T. Cox, J. Peele, E. Symon, S. Noble, R. Williamson, T. Wotton, D. Browne, B. Creake, J. Clarke, R. Hett, T. Osborne, L. Gilliver, J. Stagg", "label": [[12, 27, "PERSON"], [28, 43, "PERSON"], [44, 61, "ORG"], [63, 74, "PERSON"], [76, 86, "PERSON"], [88, 96, "PERSON"], [98, 108, "PERSON"], [110, 134, "ORG"], [136, 163, "ORG"], [165, 174, "PERSON"], [176, 186, "PERSON"], [188, 196, "PERSON"], [198, 207, "PERSON"], [209, 218, "PERSON"], [220, 228, "PERSON"], [230, 254, "ORG"], [256, 267, "PERSON"], [269, 280, "PERSON"], [282, 293, "PERSON"], [295, 303, "PERSON"], [305, 320, "PERSON"], [321, 328, "PERSON"], [330, 337, "PERSON"], [339, 351, "PERSON"], [353, 362, "PERSON"], [364, 370, "PERSON"], [372, 380, "PERSON"], [382, 390, "PERSON"], [392, 400, "PERSON"], [402, 415, "PERSON"], [417, 426, "PERSON"], [428, 437, "PERSON"], [439, 448, "PERSON"], [450, 459, "PERSON"], [461, 468, "PERSON"], [470, 480, "PERSON"], [482, 493, "PERSON"], [495, 503, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 153, "data": "printed for T. Osborne, in Gray's-Inn", "label": [[12, 22, "PERSON"], [27, 37, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 154, "data": "printed for T. Warner", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 155, "data": "printed for J. Peele at Locke's Head in Pater-Noster Row", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [24, 36, "LOC"], [40, 56, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 156, "data": "typis Gul. Bowyer. Impensis G. Strahan ad Insigne Globi aurati e regione Excambii Regalis", "label": [[6, 17, "PERSON"], [28, 38, "PERSON"], [50, 62, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 157, "data": "printed for T. Warner, at the Black-Boy in Paternoster-Row", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [43, 58, "LOC"], [26, 39, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 158, "data": "printed by W. Bowyer", "label": [[11, 20, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 159, "data": "printed for S.C. and sold by H. Cooke, near Water-Lane, Fleet-Street, E. Lynn, over-against Deveraux-Court, without Temple-Bar", "label": [[12, 16, "PERSON"], [29, 37, "PERSON"], [44, 54, "LOC"], [56, 68, "LOC"], [70, 77, "PERSON"], [92, 106, "LOC"], [116, 126, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 160, "data": "s.n", "label": []}
{"id": 161, "data": "typis Gul. Bowyer, sen. & jun. Prostat venalis apud Gul. Thurlbourn Cantabrigensem, R. Clements Oxoniensem, & bibliopolas Londinenses", "label": [[6, 30, "ORG"], [52, 67, "PERSON"], [84, 95, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 162, "data": "s.n", "label": []}
{"id": 163, "data": "s.n", "label": []}
{"id": 164, "data": "s.n", "label": []}
{"id": 165, "data": "s.n", "label": []}
{"id": 166, "data": "s.n", "label": []}
{"id": 167, "data": "printed by W. Bowyer: and sold by J. and J. Knapton, A. Bettesworth, J. Osborn and Tho. Longman, J. Noon, and J. Clark, at the Royal-Exchange", "label": [[11, 20, "PERSON"], [34, 51, "ORG"], [53, 67, "PERSON"], [69, 95, "ORG"], [97, 104, "PERSON"], [110, 118, "PERSON"], [123, 141, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 168, "data": "printed for Charles King in Westminster-Hall", "label": [[12, 24, "PERSON"], [28, 44, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 169, "data": "printed for the author, and sold by W. Innys, at the West End of St. Paul's", "label": [[36, 44, "PERSON"], [53, 75, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 170, "data": "pour Jean Pierre Coderc, Marchand Libraire, in Little-Newport-Street, à la tête de Pline", "label": [[5, 23, "PERSON"], [47, 68, "LOC"], [72, 88, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 171, "data": "printed for T. Worrall at the Judge's-Head, over-against St. Dunstan's Church, Fleet-Street", "label": [[12, 22, "PERSON"], [26, 42, "LOC"], [57, 77, "LOC"], [79, 91, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 172, "data": "printed for Francis Cogan, at the Middle-Temple-Gate in Fleet-Street", "label": [[12, 25, "PERSON"], [34, 52, "LOC"], [56, 68, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 173, "data": "printed by W. Bowyer, for Fletcher Gyles over-against Gray's-Inn in Holborn", "label": [[11, 20, "PERSON"], [26, 40, "PERSON"], [54, 64, "LOC"], [68, 75, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 174, "data": "e Theatro Sheldoniano", "label": [[2, 21, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 175, "data": "e Theatro Sheldoniano", "label": [[2, 21, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 176, "data": "printed by W. Bowyer for J. Senex, at the Globe in Fleet-Street, J. Osborn and T. Longman at the Ship in Pater-Noster-Row; and W. Innys in St. Paul's Church Yard", "label": [[11, 20, "PERSON"], [25, 33, "PERSON"], [38, 47, "LOC"], [51, 63, "LOC"], [65, 89, "ORG"], [93, 101, "LOC"], [105, 121, "LOC"], [127, 135, "PERSON"], [139, 161, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 177, "data": "printed for B. Motte, at the Middle-Temple Gate in Fleet-Street", "label": [[12, 20, "PERSON"], [29, 47, "LOC"], [51, 63, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 178, "data": "printed for G. Strahan against the Royal Exchange in Cornhill, Richard Williamson near Grays-Inn-Gate in Holborn, and T. Osborne near Grays-Inn Walks", "label": [[12, 22, "PERSON"], [31, 49, "LOC"], [53, 61, "LOC"], [63, 81, "PERSON"], [87, 101, "LOC"], [105, 112, "LOC"], [118, 128, "PERSON"], [134, 149, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 179, "data": "printed by B. S. in the year", "label": [[11, 16, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 180, "data": "typis Gulielmi Bowyer", "label": [[6, 21, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 181, "data": "e Theatro Sheldoniano, MDCCXXX. Impensis Davidis Lyon", "label": [[2, 21, "LOC"], [41, 53, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 182, "data": "Impressa anno", "label": []}
{"id": 183, "data": "printed for James and John Knapton, John Darby, Arthur Bettesworth, Edmund Parker, Francis Fayram, John Pemberton, John Osborn and Thomas Longman, Charles Rivington, Benjamin Motte, Francis Clay, Jeremiah Batley, and Aaron Ward", "label": [[12, 34, "ORG"], [36, 46, "PERSON"], [48, 66, "PERSON"], [68, 81, "PERSON"], [83, 97, "PERSON"], [99, 113, "PERSON"], [115, 145, "ORG"], [147, 164, "PERSON"], [166, 180, "PERSON"], [182, 194, "PERSON"], [196, 211, "PERSON"], [217, 227, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 184, "data": "Printed for A. Millar, at Buchanan's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 41, "LOC"], [56, 76, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 185, "data": "s.n", "label": []}
{"id": 186, "data": "printed for A. Millar, at Buchman's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 40, "LOC"], [55, 75, "LOC"], [79, 89, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 187, "data": "Printed for A. Millar, at Buchanan's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 41, "LOC"], [56, 76, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 188, "data": "Printed for A. Millar, at Buchanan's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 41, "LOC"], [56, 76, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 189, "data": "printed for A. Millar", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 190, "data": "printed for A. Millar, at Buchanan's Head, over-against St. Clement's Church in the Strand", "label": [[12, 21, "PERSON"], [26, 41, "LOC"], [56, 76, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"]]}
